Product

Solutions

Resources

English (US)EspañolPortuguêsFrançaisDeutschItalianoPolskiNederlandsSrpski

EN (US)ESPTFRDEITPLNLSR

Product  

Solutions  

Resources  

Privacy Policy
==============

Last Updated: January 31st, 2023

This privacy policy will explain how we use the personal data we collect from you when you use our website:[ideabuddy.com](https://ideabuddy.com/)In this Policy “we”, “us”, “our” refer to the IdeaBuddy team. We are committed to protecting the privacy of our website visitors and to protect data of our subscribers.

Topics:1. What data do we collect?
2. How do we collect your data?
3. How will we use your data?
4. How long do we store your data?
5. What are your data protection rights?
6. Are your ideas safe with IdeaBuddy?
7. What are cookies?
8. How do we use cookies?
9. What types of cookies do we use?
10. How to manage your cookies
11. Privacy policies of other websites
12. Changes to our privacy policy
13. How to contact us
14. Our details

By reading this Privacy Policy, you give your Consent on all the topics stated in the Policy. If you do not agree with any of the stated formulations, please do not use our Website, Service or any of its features offered.

1\. What data do we collect?
----------------------------

We collect the following data:* Personal identification information (Name, email address).
* Your IP address, geographical location, browser type, and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation paths, information about the timing, frequency and pattern of your service use. The source of this usage data is Google Analytics.

The legal basis for this processing is consent.

2\. How do we collect your data?
--------------------------------

You directly provide us with the data we collect. We collect data and process data when you:* Register for free trial and test of the IdeaBuddy application;
* Voluntarily complete a customer survey or provide feedback on any of our message boards or via email;
* Use or view our website via your browser’s cookies;
* Google analytics.

3\. How will we use your data?
------------------------------

We collect your data so that we can:* Email you info on the upcoming updates of the web application
* Offer you a subscription to our Newsletter and/or for the purpose of emailing you the relevant notifications
* Analyze the use of the website and services
* Secure: operating of our website, providing our services, ensuring the security of our website and services, maintaining back-ups of our databases and communicating with you
* Process information that you post for publication on our support portal or through our service. Your data may be processed for the purposes of enabling such publication and administering our website and services.
* Provide technical and customer support, offering, marketing and selling relevant goods and/or services to you.

We may process any of your personal data identified in this policy where necessary for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims, whether in court proceedings or in an administrative or out-of-court procedure. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, i.e. the protection and assertion of our legal rights, your legal rights and the legal rights of others. Also, your data can be processed where necessary for the purposes of obtaining or maintaining insurance coverage, managing risks, or obtaining professional advice. The legal basis for this processing is our legitimate interests, namely the proper protection of our business against risks.

We can also use any of your personal data where its processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.

If you agree, we will share your data with our third-party partner companies solely to enable them to perform specific services for us. Those services made on our behalf may include:* Assisting us with sending marketing emails and performing social network tracking;
* Providing cloud storage services;
* Serving advertisements;
* Providing customer support services;
* Enabling us to send you emails;
* Providing web analytics, performance tracking, and email automation software;
* Providing subscription management, payment gateway integration, and invoicing services;
* Providing video streaming services;
* Providing issue-tracking software;
* Monitoring errors on web platforms;
* Offering marketing and advertising services;
* Assisting appointment scheduling;
* Providing online survey software;
* Providing web conferencing services.

The legal basis for this processing is consent.

4\. How long do we store your data?
-----------------------------------

Personal data that we process for any purpose or purposes shall not be kept for longer than is necessary for that purpose or those purposes. We will keep your personal data for a period of 12 months. Once this time period has expired, we will delete your data from our system unless you opt to prolong the use of IdeaBuddy application or other website features such as Blog, Newsletter, etc. further on.

We may retain your personal data where such retention is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or in order to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of another natural person.

5\. What are your data protection rights?
-----------------------------------------

Our Company would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:

The right to access – You have the right to request us for copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.

The right to rectification – You have the right to request that Our Company correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request us to complete the information you believe is incomplete.

The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.

The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.

The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.

The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.

If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us at our email:[\[email protected\]](https://ideabuddy.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

6\. Are your ideas safe with IdeaBuddy?
---------------------------------------

Your ideas will remain secure and completely confidential. The encryption process protects your private data 24/7, so no one can access it without your permission.

Deep Blue Sea Studio does not claim any ownership in any of the content, including any of your business ideas, text, data, information, images, photographs, music, sound, video, or other material, that you enter, upload, transmit, or store in your IdeaBuddy account. your ideas will remain secure and completely confidential. the encryption process protects your private data 24/7, so no one can access it without your permission.

All of the entries and uploads in your IdeaBuddy account will be stored one month after the expiry of your subscription and then will be deleted permanently.

7\. Cookies
-----------

Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information. When you visit our websites, we may collect information from you automatically through cookies or similar technology.

For further information, visit[allaboutcookies.org](https://allaboutcookies.org/).

8\. How do we use cookies?
--------------------------

We use cookies in a range of ways to improve your experience on our website, including:* Keeping you signed in
* Understanding how you use our website

9\. What types of cookies do we use?
------------------------------------

There are a number of different types of cookies, however, our website uses:* Functionality – we use these cookies so that we recognize you on our website and remember your previously selected preferences. These could include what language you prefer and location you are in. A mix of first-party and third-party cookies are used
* Advertising – we use these cookies to collect information about your visit to our website, the content you viewed, the links you followed and information about your browser, device, and your IP address. We sometimes share some limited aspects of this data with third parties for advertising purposes. We may also share online data collected through cookies with our advertising partners. This means that when you visit another website, you may be shown advertising based on your browsing patterns on our website
* Statistic – we may use these cookies to collect information used in aggregate form to help us understand how our website is being used, or how effective our marketing campaigns are.
* Necessary – after the launch of the commercial subscription plans for our application, these cookies are required for technical reasons.

10\. How to manage cookies
--------------------------

You can set your browser not to accept cookies, and for more information on this, please refer to our[Cookie Statement](https://ideabuddy.com/cookie-statement/). However, in a few cases, some of our website features may not function as a result.

11\. Privacy policies of other websites
---------------------------------------

Our website can contain links to other websites. Our privacy policy applies only to our website, so if you click on a link to another website, you should read their privacy policy.

12\. Changes to our privacy policy
----------------------------------

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we place any updates on this web page. Please refer to “Last updated” in the beginning of this document.

13\. How to contact us
----------------------

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, the data we hold on you, or you would like to exercise one of your data protection rights, please do not hesitate to email us on:[\[email protected\]](https://ideabuddy.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

14\. Our details
----------------

1. This website is owned and operated by Deep Blue Sea Studio DOO.
2. We are registered in Serbia under registration number 21506532.
3. You can contact us by using our website contact form.

All-in-one business planning software, powered by AI

Product

Product  

Solutions

Solutions  

Resources

Resources  

Company

Contact Us

Company  

Contact Us

Follow us

© IdeaBuddy 2024, All Rights Reserved
